{
    "results": [
        {
            "question": "Computer virus is?",
            "correct_answer": "Software",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Freeware",
                "Hardware",
                "Bacteria"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Filter is available on?",
            "correct_answer": "Data menu",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Tools menu",
                "View menu",
                "Edit menu"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Font folder is located on:",
            "correct_answer": "Control Panel folder",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Program folder",
                "MS Word file",
                "Desktop folder"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which application program is called data base program?",
            "correct_answer": "Access",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Excel",
                "Word",
                "PowerPoint"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one is not relationship type?",
            "correct_answer": "Many to one",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Many to many",
                "One to many",
                "One to one"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one is not database object?",
            "correct_answer": "Datasheet",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Form",
                "Table",
                "Report"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The technology is used in CD-ROM.",
            "correct_answer": "Optical",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Magnetic",
                "Mechanical",
                "Electro-mechanical"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which code is used in keystroke?",
            "correct_answer": "ASCII",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "ANSI",
                "Both",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Www stands for?",
            "correct_answer": "World Wide Web",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "World Wide Work",
                "World Wide Webpage",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "The fastest printer is?",
            "correct_answer": "Laser printer",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Dot matrix printer",
                "Inkjet printer",
                "None of theme"
            ]
        }
    ]
}